<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Ify</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Ify</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Soliloquy of Stanley (SSS)</title>
      <link>/2020/09/26/summer-soliloquy-of-stanley-sss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/26/summer-soliloquy-of-stanley-sss/</guid>
      <description>Moving on to the next chapter...
As I look onward to the next chapter of my life. I wanted to briefly pen down some couple of undocumented reflection that has been a foreplay in my thought process this summer.
It has been two years since I was given this wonderful opportunity to dream. First, I am grateful to IMBRSea for this incredible platform to ride of the crest of what was once a mere wishful thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From the Shell</title>
      <link>/2020/09/09/from-the-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/09/from-the-shell/</guid>
      <description>Why this? Why write?
Honestly, I never meant to go this way. I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure why I am doing this. I have been much of a recluse for long to suddenly charge off to the internet to start anything remotely close to blogging. However, during the summer of 2020 amidst the COVID pandemic, I became too bored and I decided to learn some new stuff. The highlight were improving on my web dev skills, tried to get my head around Latex, checkout the much talk about Julia Language, had a go with some good O&amp;rsquo;l Fortran and lastly found time to engage in some summer reading (non-science books).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Stanley. I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in Laboratoire des Sciences du Climat et de l&amp;rsquo;Environnement (LSCE). My overarching interest lies in the intersection of physics, ecology and biogeochemistry in the marine environment. Currently, I will be working on aspect of sediment biogeochemical modelling.
I decided to create this space as a landing page for my work. Occassionally, I will share some personal experiences/story as I journey on this academic terrain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/</guid>
      <description>Previous project These are some recent project I have worked or still working on.
  Investigating Coral Community Change and Potential Recovery Following Mass Coral Bleaching and Mortality Event-Chagos Archipelagos case study
 Involved in project investigating the response of coral communities after episodic external disturbances with the charming Dr Catherine Head of University of Oxford, UK as part of my professional practice in the International Masters in Marine Biological resources programme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>